<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Quizlet App</string>
    <string name="login_screen">Login</string>
    <string name="change_username">CHANGE USERNAME</string>
    <string name="change_email">CHANGE EMAIL</string>
    <string name="change_password">CHANGE PASSWORD</string>
    <string name="about_app">About app</string>
    <string name="about_app_content">Effective Date: April 2, 2015; Last Updated: April 14, 2022The Quizlet, Inc. Website and its applications are a hosted service operated by Quizlet, Inc.(Service). Any use of the Service is subject to the following Terms and Conditions of Service(Terms of Service or Terms), as well as to Quizlet Privacy Policy, Quizlet Community Guidelines, and Quizlet Honor Code, all of which are incorporated by reference into these Terms of Service. Your use of theService will constitute your acceptance of these Terms of Service.Eligibility. Use of the Service is void where prohibited. The Service is intended for users over the age of 13, but is open to all ages. For children age 13 or younger (or other age of consent where required by local law), Quizlet offers a restricted feature set and website experience that removes certain features. By using the Service, you represent and warrant that (a) all registration information you submit is truthful and accurate; (b) you will maintain the accuracy of such information; and (c) your use of the Service does not violate any applicable law or regulation.Your Quizlet Account and Data. If you create an account on the Service, you are responsible for maintaining the security of your account and data, and you are fully responsible for all activities that occur under the account. Accounts are for individual, not organizational, use by a single person only. You may not share your account with any other person. You must notify Quizlet immediately of any unauthorized uses of your data, your account or any other breaches of security. Quizlet will not be liable for any acts or omissions by you, including any damages of any kind incurred as a result of such acts or omissions. Quizlet may from time to time set storage limits for your data, or take any other measures it considers appropriate to manage the Service. Quizlet may also from time to time change its policies on offering commercial content or displaying advertising, and may do this without notice.Subscriptions. You have the option to purchase a subscription plan, which offers an upgraded experience with additional features or functionality for your Quizlet account (Subscription). Subscriptions may be purchased either by (i) paying a recurring subscription fee; or (ii) pre-payment giving you access for a specific time period (Pre-Paid Period). The terms stated below will govern your participation in these programs.Pre-Paid Subscription Term: Subscriptions purchased for a Pre-Paid Period will automatically terminate at the end of the Pre-Paid Period.Group Orders:A Group Order provides discounted credits towards multiple, individual Pre-Paid Period Subscriptions via a unique upgrade link. You may select the number of subscription credits you would like to purchase. Purchasers of Group Orders are solely responsible for the distribution of subscription credits. All subscriptions are non-transferable and irrevocable once a credit has been redeemed by an individual user account. Individual accounts which use a Group Order subscription credit may not be associated with any school, business, entity, institution or any other centralized account and the purchaser of the Group Order has no right to or interest in any account to which a subscription credit has been applied, except where the purchaser of the Group Order and the holder of the account to which a subscription credit has been applied are the same individual.To Cancel Your Subscription: You may cancel your Subscription at any time. If your Subscription is set to automatically renew, you must cancel at least 1 day prior to the expiration of the Subscription term in order to avoid additional charges. You may continue to enjoy your Subscription benefits until that date, after which your Subscription will terminate and your account will automatically downgrade. You can cancel your Subscription in your account settings or by going here. Our cancellation policy can be found here.Cancellation by Us: We may cancel your Upgraded Membership at any time for any reason, with or without prior notice.Refunds: Except where required by law, Subscriptions purchased directly through Quizlet are non-refundable. Subscriptions purchased through other platforms are subject to the refund policies of those platforms. Quizlet cannot be held responsible for these platform policies. We do not provide any refunds if the price for Subscription plans drops, or if we offer subsequent promotion pricing or change the content or features of the Service.Price changes: We may change the price for Subscriptions from time to time. We will communicate any price changes to you in advance. Price changes for Subscriptions will take effect on the next renewal date following the date of the price change. As permitted by local law, you accept the new price by continuing to maintain your Subscription after the price change takes effect. If you do not agree with the price changes, you have the right toreject the change by canceling from the Subscription prior to the price change going into effect. Please be sure to read any such notification of price changes carefully.</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="profile">Profile</string>

    <string name="title_activity_sign_up">SignUp</string>
    <string name="title_activity_sign_in">SignIn</string>
    <string name="createSet">CREATE SET</string>
    <string name="study_set_details" />
</resources>
